疯狂杰克不仅有自己的网站
The Mad Jacks not only have a web site,
而且还有主题曲
they have a theme song.
*你需要卑鄙下流的手段时  疯狂杰克*
*When you need down and dirty action  Mad Jacks*
*保您满意  疯狂杰克*
*With a guaranteed satisfaction  Mad Jacks*
*谁可能有最出其不意的招数*
*Who's got might to the max Massive surprise attacks*
*疯狂疯狂疯狂杰克*
*Mad Mad Mad Mad Mad Mad Mad Mad Jacks*
有任务吗  不用担心
You got a mission? Don't sweat it.
我们会帮你轻而易举解决
We'll crank it up to Jacks-imum overdrive!
杰克出击
Jack attack!
疯狂杰克
Mad Jacks
疯狂杰克是一支高能行动队伍
The Mad Jacks are a high-octane action team.
他们会引起骚乱
They will wreak havoc.
疯狂杰克不会对上述骚乱负责
The Mad Jacks will not be responsible for said havoc,
但那样会很棒
but it will be awesome.